# **SHEFALI GOEL**

Mobile: +91- 9871820038 +91- 9911931660

Email Id.: shefaligoel3096@gmail.com

LinkedIn:- https://www.linkedin.com/in/shefali-goel-6b382510a/

#### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

Certified BYJU's Teacher having a Combined Experience of **Programming/Coding Languages** (**Java, JavaScript, Python, HTML, CSS)** & **Sales Understanding**. Possess excellent oral and written communication skills. In-depth understanding of **Programming/Coding Languages** as well as **Firebase Database**.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Teacher, August 2020- Present BYJU's WhiteHat Junior

#### Roles and Responsibilities:

- Teaching **Programming/Coding** Languages (**Java, JavaScript, Python, HTML, CSS**) including logics, sequences, & structures to (6-14) age group kids to generate creative outcomes like websites, animations, and apps.
- Upskilling Firebase Database knowledge of young minds with the help of interactive live sessions.
- Teaching **Mathematics** to (6-14) age group kids in an interactive manner to make the concepts easy for the kids.
- Conducting booster classes for clearing student's doubts in the fundamental concepts as well as in assigned Projects.
- Providing reports and feedback of student to their parents on regular basis.

# Business Development Executive, July 2018- January 2020 CDG Certification Ltd.

#### Roles and Responsibilities:

- To build contacts with potential clients to create new business opportunities
- Maintaining fruitful relationships with clients and address their needs effectively.
- Research and identifying new market opportunities.
- Arrange meetings for senior management with prospective clients
- To Keep prospective client database updated
- Maintaining knowledge of all product and service offerings of the company
- To Follow company guidelines and procedures for acquisition of customers, submission of tenders etc

#### **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS**

- B.Tech. (Computer Science Engineering), 2014-2018 from Satyug Darshan Institute of Engineering & Technology,
  MDU University with 82.67%
- Class XII (Higher Secondary Certificate), 2014 from St. Michael's Sr. Sec. School with 84 %
- Class X (Secondary School Certificate), 2002 from St. Michael's Sr. Sec. School with CGPA 9.2

#### TRAINING/INTERNSHIP

- 1) 5 Months Training at **NS Matrix Services Pvt. Ltd.**, January-June 2018
  - Technical Scripting using languages like Decipher, Python, JavaScript, CSS, HTML.
  - Understanding client's requirement

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Core JAVA
- PYTHON
- C, C++
- CSS
- JavaScript
- HTML
- Decipher
- Operating System: Windows & Unix
- Basic Computer skills like Microsoft Office

## **PROJECTS**

- 1) **COLLEGE MANAGEMENT SYSTEM,** as Team Project (January- April 2017).
- Designed webpages using HTML, CSS
- This project was capable to manage the database of various departments of college.
- 2) Project on Online Survey and Market Research, (January- June 2018)
  - Building of the survey as per customer requirement.
  - Testing of this survey.
  - Processing the data of the survey

### **EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

- Vice President of 'BYTES CLUB' in the college
- Active member of 'HAPPY CLUB' in the college.
- Cultural minister of the school for a year (2013-2014).
- Organized various cultural events in school and college.
- Won many prizes in cultural and sports event in-inter and intra, school and college.
- Won second prize in interschool report writing competition in class 10.

#### **PERSONAL DETAILS**

Father's Name : Mr. Pawan Goyal Mother's Name : Mrs. Anju Goyal Date of Birth : 30<sup>th</sup> October 1996

Nationality : Indian

Languages : English & Hindi